Guide to the Abraham Hayward correspondence files: 1063 items, 1790-1889
The New York Public Library. Carl H. Pforzheimer Collection of Shelley and His Circle.
- Torrington, George Byng, Viscount, 1812-1884, Union Club - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 15 February 1872; HWD 02.068; autograph letter signed
- Torrington, George Byng, Viscount, 1812-1884, 4 Warwick Square S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 February 1868; HWD 02.069; autograph letter signed
- Torrington, George Byng, Viscount, 1812-1884, 4, Warwick Square S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 June 1857; HWD 10.050; autograph letter signed
- Trench, Richard Chenevix, 1807-1886, Westminster - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 November 1861; MISC 3518; autograph letter signed
- Truro, Thomas Wilde, Baron, 1782-1855, Stanhope Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 September 1846; MISC 3502; autograph letter signed
- Tyndall, John, 1820-1893, Royal Institution of Great Britain - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 25 November 1871; HWD 10.106; autograph letter signed
- Van de Weyer, Jean-Sylvain, 1802-1874, New Lodge Windsor Forest - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 November 1871; HWD 02.067; autograph letter signed
- Van de Weyer, Jean-Sylvain, 1802-1874, 21 Arlington St. S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 June 1871; HWD 02.062; autograph letter signed
- Van de Weyer, Jean-Sylvain, 1802-1874 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 January 1863; HWD 03.090; autograph letter signed
- Van de Weyer, Jean-Sylvain, 1802-1874, New Lodge, Windsor Forest - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 April [no year]; HWD 06.065; autograph letter signed
- Van de Weyer, Jean-Sylvain, 1802-1874, New Lodge, Windsor Forest - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1861; HWD 03.088; autograph letter signed
- Van de Weyer, Jean-Sylvain, 1802-1874, 21 Arlington St S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 20 July 1869; HWD 03.025; autograph letter signed
- Van de Weyer, Jean-Sylvain, 1802-1874, New Lodge Windsor Forest - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 31 October 1872; HWD 02.066; autograph letter signed
- Ventry, Harriet Elizabeth Frances Wauchope, Baroness, 1828-1906 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Sunday"; HWD 07.019; autograph letter signed
- Villiers, Charles Pelham, 1802-1898, Traveller's Club, S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 09.061; autograph letter signed
- Villiers, Charles Pelham, 1802-1898 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 05.091; autograph letter signed
- Villiers, Charles Pelham, 1802-1898 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 06.064; autograph letter signed
- Vogue, Achille, 28 Charter House Square, London - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 March 1869; HWD 10.034; autograph letter signed
- Waldegrave, Frances Elizabeth Anne (Braham), Countess of, 1821-1879, Phoenix Park, Dublin - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 February 1866; HWD 03.022; autograph letter signed
  Signed "Frances, Countess of Waldegrave".
- Walpole, Spencer H. (Spencer Horatio), 1806-1898, 109 Eaton Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 April 1879; HWD 09.054; autograph letter signed
- Walpole, Spencer H. (Spencer Horatio), 1806-1898, Newstead Abbey, Nottingham - to [?], 10 January 1889; HWD 01.007; autograph letter signed
- Webb, Emilia Jane, 1826-1889 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 26 February 1878; HWD 03.035; autograph letter signed
- Westmorland, John Fane, Earl of, 1784-1859 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 19 February 1857; HWD 03.089; autograph letter signed
- Westmorland, Priscilla Anne Fane, Countess of, 1793-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 December 1874; HWD 03.019; autograph letter signed
  Signed "Lady Westmoreland".
- Wilberforce, Samuel, 1805-1873, Cuddeston Palace, Wheatley, Oxon - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 January 1857; HWD 03.069; autograph letter signed
- Williams-Wynn, Marie Emily, d. 1905, 18 St. James's Square S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 09.077; autograph letter signed
- Winchilsea, George James Finch-Hatton, Earl of, 1815-1887, Whites Club - to "Editor of the Morning Chronicle", 7 July 1851; HWD 06.072; autograph letter 3rd person
  "Lord Maidstone presents his compts".
- Wortley, Jane Stuart, 1820-1900, 5 Mandeville Place, Manchester Square W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 25 January [no year]; HWD 09.084; autograph letter signed
- Wyke, Charles Lennox, Sir, 1815-1897 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 July 1866; HWD 01.096; autograph letter signed
- Wyke, Charles Lennox, Sir, 1815-1897, Copenhagen - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 May 1873; HWD 01.075; autograph letter signed
- Wynne, Mary Anne Frances Haggitt, 7 Eaton Place S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Ash Wednesday"; HWD 05.079; autograph letter signed
- [?], Somerset House - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 January 1856; HWD 08.015; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.049; autograph letter signed
- [?], Chatsworth House - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1 October 1884; HWD 06.040; envelope only
- [?] - to [Mrs. H. Mecreler?], 27 December 1869; HWD 04.099; [clippings in envelope]
  Addressed to Lynne Regis, Dorcetshire; with manuscript clippings, including autographs of geologist H. T. De La Beche and naval captain Matthew Liddou.
- [?], 13 Albert Terrace Knightsbridge - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 February 1875; HWD 06.036; autograph letter signed
  As of 1870 this address was the home of Lord Lennox.
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 02.001
  Notes on 10-21 July 1690, in French, [Aumale?].
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 January 1841; HWD 10.098; envelope only
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 08.007; autograph letter signed
- [?], HWD 06.105; notes
  Begins: "M [C?] Villiers / That it / is the opinion of this, However ...".
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.058; autograph letter signed
- [?], 170 Piccadilly - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.102; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.092; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 20 January 1836; HWD 10.104; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.005; autograph letter signed
  "Virginia" embossed at head of stationery.
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 May 1847; HWD 07.006; autograph letter signed
- [?], German Embassy, 9 Carlton House Terrace, S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 January 1875; HWD 01.069; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Sunday"; HWD 07.012; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Thursday"; HWD 07.014; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to [?], HWD 07.020; autograph letter fragment?
  including, "lovely Mrs. Cornwallis West must be [pleasured?] at having such verses written [?] by Mr. Hayward".
- [?] [G. T. Porter], HWD 10.076; envelope only
- [?], 9 Belgrave Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 03.038; autograph letter signed
  gold-stamped "Belgrave Square" stationery.
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 January 1878; HWD 07.056; autograph letter signed
- [?], Speaker's Court, Palace of Westminster S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 February [no year]; HWD 03.041; autograph letter signed
  Speaker's Court stationery.
- [?] - to Winchilsea, Constance Henrietta Paget Finch, Countess of, d. 1878, HWD 05.028; autograph letter signed
  with gilt embossed "X" on cardstock stationery.
- [?], Paris - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 November 1862; HWD 05.068; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.004; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.006
  Extract from Junius attack on the King.
  Copy in unknown hand.
- [?], Woburn Abbey - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 18 December 1855; MISC 3528; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 09.075; autograph letter signed
  "FR" (or "RF") on stationery.
- [?], Hereford House, Park Street W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 October 1883; HWD 04.015; autograph letter signed
- [?], Gumley Hall, Rugby - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 15 February 1863; HWD 04.016; autograph letter signed
- [?], Lord Chamberlain's Office, St. James's Palace S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 February [no year]; HWD 07.079; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 April 1861; HWD 07.052; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.034; [envelope only]
  [empty envelope].
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 June 1847; HWD 04.091; autograph letter signed
- [?], 23 Heumarket, Vienna - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 5 December 1876; HWD 10.044; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 January 1843; HWD 06.039; envelope only
  with wax seal; initials "A" and "O" intertwined.
- [?], 29 Eaton Square, S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 April 1863; HWD 05.060; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 06.087; autograph letter
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 5 April [no year]; HWD 04.065; autograph letter signed
- [?], 105 Piccadilly - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.095; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 06.090; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 June [?] [no year]; HWD 04.078; autograph letter signed
- [?], 10 William St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 09.103; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.082; autograph letter signed
  Monday, 11th [June?]; Printed stationery: 13, Park Place, St. James's.
- [?], 39 Lowndes Street S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, Feby 3rd; HWD 04.083; autograph letter signed
- [?], The Deanery, Chester - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 August 1869; HWD 10.003; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.035; [envelope only]
  [empty letter cover].
- [?], Bell & Co, Madrid - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 October 1868; HWD 09.015; autograph letter
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 August 1859; HWD 09.022; autograph letter signed
- [?], 22 [Burton?] St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.033; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 January 1856; HWD 08.080; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 August 1851; HWD 07.034; autograph letter signed
  with inserted blue slip with writing in what appears to be another hand.
- [?], 26 Wilton Crescent, London - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 April [no year]; HWD 03.077; autograph letter signed
  26 Wilton Crescent stationery.
- [?] Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884 - poem, "Thou would' st be mine own", HWD 03.092; manuscript
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 January 1862; HWD 10.059; envelope only
- [?] - to [John Bennett], 17 February 1845; HWD 09.052; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 July 1869; HWD 10.040; autograph letter signed
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 May 1863; HWD 09.030; envelope only
- [?], 80, South Audley Street, W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Tuesday"; HWD 07.024; autograph letter signed
- [?], 42 Rue d. l. Madeleine, Paris - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 February 1846; HWD 07.038; letter (copy)
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 November 1868; HWD 10.055; envelope only
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.098; [empty envelope]
  With red wax seal.
- [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 31 January [w/m = 1874]; HWD 03.044; autograph letter signed
  [elf seal on stationery].
- [?], Studley Park - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 October 1855; HWD 09.047; autograph letter (fragment?)
- [A G A Mcaroeeg], 35 Chester Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 May [no year]; HWD 03.036; autograph letter signed
- [A. D. Junder?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Tuesday 18 J[a/u]n"; HWD 07.029; autograph letter signed
- [A. Dartriz?], 30, Curzon Street W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.059; autograph letter signed
- [A. Deillergan?, Esq.], 91 Adelaide Road, N. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 June 1865; HWD 06.051; autograph letter signed
  within letter cover addressed to [Deillergan?].
- [A. Harvey], Ickwell Bury Biggleswade - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 January 1878; HWD 04.032; autograph letter signed
- [A - ? Sothenham?], No. 70 Mount Street, Grosvenor Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.090; autograph letter signed
- [Adeline Wolff], 25 Alhert Gate - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 February 1878; HWD 07.066; autograph letter signed
- [Alia? de Rothschild] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 February 1878; HWD 05.073; autograph letter signed
- [Alya Neuhoff?], 48 Dover St. Picadilly - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 November 1882; HWD 01.006; autograph letter signed
- [Amelia, Princess of Schleswid-Holstein] - to [?], MISC 3533; autograph
- [Amy?], 17 Charles Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.096; autograph letter signed
- [Andrieau?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 December 1857; HWD 01.089; autograph letter signed
  In French.
- [Andrieau?], Vienna, Bastey 803 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 December 1855; HWD 01.091; autograph letter signed
- [Anna Lamb] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 December 1846; HWD 02.024; autograph letter signed
- [Anna Lindsay] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 02.011; autograph letter signed
- [Anne Dicey?], 67, Cadogan Place, S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 January 1878; HWD 05.081; autograph letter signed
- [Annie Braphy?], 24 Park Lane - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.002; autograph letter signed
  at 24 Park Lane.
- [Annie Elcho] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 March 1855; HWD 09.085; autograph letter signed
- [Annie Twiss] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.010; autograph letter signed
- [Anti-Cant?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 March [no year]; HWD 02.010; autograph letter signed
- [Aug. Stafford] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 July 1855; HWD 04.064; autograph letter signed
- [Augusta Davenport], 11, Upper Eccleston Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 February, Saturday; HWD 05.077; autograph letter signed
- [B. Lubome?], Sherborne Park, Northleach, Cheltenham - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 February [no year]; HWD 07.065; autograph letter signed
- [Beatrice Campbell], Widdington [?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 26 June 1847; HWD 07.017; autograph letter signed
- [Beaumont], Bretton Park, Wakefield - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 January [no year]; HWD 09.029; autograph letter signed
- [Blackie?], Hotel Klee - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 April [no year]; HWD 04.049; autograph letter signed
- [Blackie] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 March [no year]; HWD 04.062; autograph letter signed
- [Blanche Agibry?], Cortadu Castle - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 28 February 1878; HWD 07.072; autograph letter signed
- [Blanche Lindsay], 4 Cromwell Place, South Kensington - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 February [no year]; HWD 09.087; autograph letter signed
- [Brownrigg] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 26 June [no year]; HWD 04.102; autograph letter signed
- [Bru?], Corsham Court, Chippenham - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 January 1859; HWD 09.018; autograph letter signed
- [Bullow], 62 Wimpole Street W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Monday"; HWD 04.048; autograph letter signed
- [C. Ecces?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 5 July 1853; HWD 04.070; autograph letter signed
- [C. Francis], 11 New Square, Lincoln Inn - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 January 1856; HWD 09.017; autograph letter signed
- [C. H B - bridge?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 20 May 1863; HWD 09.093; autograph letter signed
- [C. Ld. Bou?? al?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.040; autograph letter signed
- [C. Murray], Stanhope Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 May [no year]; HWD 07.011; autograph letter signed
- [C. S. V. Vane], Battle Abbey, Battle - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 May 1859; HWD 04.053; autograph letter signed
- [C. Steperly?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.032; autograph letter signed
- [C. V. de Areos?], 21 Wilton Crescent - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.062; autograph letter signed
- [Captain?? Hall] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 18 June 1841; HWD 08.030; autograph letter third person
- [Carline Morsbrone?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.073; autograph letter signed
- [Caroline Davenport Bromley], 12, Montagu Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Sunday night"; HWD 07.080; autograph letter signed
- [Catharine Vescharge?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.007; autograph letter signed
- [Caudida Bartolucci] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 May [no year]; HWD 04.057; autograph letter signed
- [Caudida Bartolucci], 111 Gloucester Rd - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 09.078; autograph letter signed
- [Ch. Bernsdorff?], Linton Park, Maidstone - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 December 1870; HWD 02.058; autograph letter signed
- [Charles O. Gorsford], Portman Lodge - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 January 1868; HWD 06.086; autograph letter signed
- [Charles Ross?], 60 Portland Hall - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 20 April 1858; HWD 06.068; autograph letter signed
- [Charles Ross?], 60 Portland Hall - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 September 1858; HWD 06.069; autograph letter signed
- [Charlles Porter Cooper], London Inn - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 January 1868; HWD 09.081; autograph letter signed
- [Chisted - - ?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 19 January 1860; HWD 05.084; autograph letter signed
- [Cilda?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Sunday"; HWD 09.046; autograph letter signed
- [Cl down?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.092; autograph letter signed
- [Clive Seb - lis?], Beechwood Dunstable - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, Sunday 11th; HWD 09.104; autograph letter signed
- [Colonel de B - - Montauban?], Brighton, 8 London Road - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 June [no year]; MISC 3531; autograph letter signed
- [Cornelius Ritchie?]: - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Thursday"; HWD 04.051; autograph letter signed
- [Corry Corneille], Mount Henry Portarlington - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 5 January 1868; HWD 01.090; autograph letter signed
- [Corry Corneille] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Thursday morning"; HWD 07.045; autograph letter signed
- [Corry Corneille] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 June 1868; HWD 02.071; autograph letter signed
- [Countess Della Torre] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 January 1859; MISC 3530; autograph letter signed
- [D. Nevill?], 45, Charles Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.064; autograph letter signed
- [Daphny Dalrymple] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.092; autograph letter signed
- [David Dandas?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 January 1856; HWD 02.051; autograph letter signed
- [De L - -?], Paris - to [?], 29 May 1843; HWD 08.035; autograph letter signed
- [Delaniere?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.080; autograph letter signed
  from Vale Royal, Norwich: "Tuesday".
- [Deurian?], East Bank - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 5 September 1869; HWD 08.039; autograph letter signed
- [Doneraile], Doneraile Court - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 April 1878; HWD 07.100; autograph letter signed
- [Dr. Huddleston], [Grydyes?] Lodgings, Lincoln - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Friday 26"; HWD 07.102; autograph letter signed
- [Dr. Stephen Linshington?], Great George St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 28 April 1845; HWD 06.103; autograph letter signed
- [Dr. Whitwell?], Trinity Lodge, Cambridge - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 March 1861; HWD 01.005; autograph letter signed
- [E. Budeley?], Temple - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 January 1856; HWD 04.033; autograph letter signed
- [E. L. Loghe?], Copenhagen - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 February 1874; HWD 01.070; autograph letter signed
- [E. Lamberton] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, Saturday 18th; HWD 05.070; autograph letter signed
- [E. Lloyd] - to [?], HWD 06.082; autograph letter
  "Ancharad" stamped and colored device on stationery.
- [E. M. Childe?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.043; autograph letter signed
- [E. M. Chresdowe?], Bell & Co, Madrin - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 26 September 1868; HWD 10.051; autograph letter signed
- [E. M. Chresdowe?], Bell & Co, Madrin - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 September 1868; HWD 10.038; autograph letter signed
- [E. Mayer] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, July 1847; HWD 07.083; autograph letter signed
- [E. Seymour], 35 Montegue Place, Russell Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Monday"; HWD 07.044; autograph letter signed
- [Edward Everett], Grosvenor Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 March 1844; HWD 02.078; autograph letter signed
- [Edward Lucas], Castle Shane Monahan - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 October 1870; HWD 05.097; autograph letter signed
- [Edwd. Holt?], 2 Cardwell [ - -?] Park - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 October 1860; HWD 08.051; autograph letter signed
- [Eile?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 July 1856; HWD 02.086; autograph letter signed
- [Elise Lenor?], 5 Chapel Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 5 February 1878; HWD 03.021; autograph letter signed
- [Elise Stonor?], 78 South Audley Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.070; autograph letter signed
- [Elizabeth De Labley?], 12 Upper Belgrave St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Weds."; HWD 07.021; autograph letter signed
- [Ellis] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 25 November 1855; HWD 04.069; autograph letter signed
- [Emily Abbott?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Thursday"; HWD 07.015; autograph letter signed
- [Emily E. Adam], 5 Landsdown Place, Brighton - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 July 1858; HWD 07.061; autograph letter signed
- [Emily Wegh?], 38 Belgrave Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 25 February [no year]; HWD 03.029; autograph letter signed
- [F. Jeffrey?] Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 02.050; fragment
- [F. Shelley?], Fulham - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 28 May 1847; HWD 03.093; autograph letter signed
- [Fanny Hayton?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 June [no year]; HWD 07.016; autograph letter signed
- [Fanny Hughes], 113 Park Street, Grosvenor Square, W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Thursday"; HWD 09.045
- [Fanny Hutt] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 May [no year]; HWD 06.026; autograph letter signed
- [Felton Hervey], Vice Regal Lodge - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 January 1855; HWD 07.033; autograph letter signed
- [Felygerall?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.042; autograph letter signed
- [Follaer?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 20 April [no year]; HWD 03.073; autograph letter signed
- [G. Grove?], Crystal Palace, S. E - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 5 May 1868; HWD 10.054; autograph letter signed